嘿
Hey.
- 你们在做什么？ - 摩妮卡逼我们看《老黄狗》
- What you guys doing?     - Monica's making us watch Old Yeller.
你们干嘛这么难过？它是《老黄狗》 非常快乐的电影
Why are you guys upset? It's Old Yeller. It's a happy movie.
- 什么？ - 你在胡说什么？
- What?     - What are you talking about?
少来了 幸福家庭养了一只狗
Come on. Happy family gets a dog.
拓荒者过得很快乐
Frontier fun!
菲比 结局呢？
Pheebs, what about the end?
老黄狗打败野狼 救了大家 大家都很快乐？
Oh, when Yeller saves the family from the wolf and everyone's happy?
结局不是那样的
That's not the end.
那时我妈会关掉电视说"剧终"
Yeah-huh. That's when my mother would shut off the TV and say, "The end."
他得了狂犬症那一段呢？
What about when he has rabies?
他没得狂犬症 他是生了宝宝
He doesn't have rabies. He has babies.
我妈是那么说的
That's what my mom said.
菲比 我想你妈不希望你看到 接下来要发生的事
Uh, Phoebe, I don't think she'd want you to see what's about to happen.
为什么？接下来会发生什么事？
Why? What's about to happen?
我没看过这个部分
I've never seen this part.
嘿 崔维斯 你拿枪做什么？
Hey, Travis, what you doing with that gun?
不
Oh, no.
不 崔维斯 把枪放下
No, no, Travis, put down the gun.
不 他是你的好朋友 他是老黄狗
No, no, he's your buddy. He's your Yeller.
不 剧终
No! The end! The end!
好吧 这是哪门子的变态狗电影？
Okay, what kind of a sick doggy snuff film is this?
没有人告诉你活着有多累
∮ So no one told you life was gonna be this way ∮
上班受罪 口袋空空 爱情变累赘
∮ Your job's a joke, you're broke, your love life's D.O.A. ∮
寂寞又潦倒 受气又受累
∮ It's like you're always stuck in second gear ∮
日复一日 年复一年
∮ When it hasn't been your day, ∮
时运不济 活着受罪
∮ your week, your month, or even your year ∮
你我永不离弃
∮ but I'll be there for you ∮
纵有狂风暴雨
∮ When the rain starts to pour ∮
你我永不离弃
∮ I'll be there for you ∮
支持一如往昔
∮ Like I've been there before ∮
你我永不离弃
∮ I'll be there for you ∮
你我相偎相依
∮ 'Cause you're there for me too ∮
你们吃了吗？理查跟我刚吃过 我们有些剩菜
Have you guys eaten? Uh, Richard and I just finished, and we've got leftovers.
鸡肉跟马铃薯
Chicken and potatoes.
我穿什么？
What am I wearing?
事实上我只戴了橡胶手套
Actually, nothing but rubber gloves.
总有一天你会真的脱光衣服 但我们不会再冲过来了
One of these times, you'll really be naked and we won't come over.
我有一条腿 三块胸肉跟一只翅膀
I got a leg, three breasts and a wing.
你怎么买得到衣服穿？
How do you find clothes that fit?
摩妮卡 我们有个问题
Oh, hey, Monica? We got a question.
对 我在健身房淋浴间 看到别的女人
All right, yes, I see other women in the shower at the gym.
不 我不会乱看
And no, I don't look.
不 不是那个问题
No, not that one.
我们在想该带谁去看《尼克队》比赛 有多一张票
We're figuring out who to bring to the Knicks game.
罗斯不能去 我们得在我的口臭朋友 艾力克普洛威
Ross can't go, so it's between my friend Eric Prower, who has breath issues...
还有爱戳人的丹之间做选择 "你看到那一球了吗？"
and Dan, with the poking. "Did you see that play?"
"还要喝啤酒吗？那是史派克李吗？"
"You want more beer? Is that Spike Lee?"
好了
Ha, ha, okay.
你们何不问理查呢？
Why don't you ask Richard?
理查 如果你多了一张《尼克队》门票…
Uh, Richard, if you had an extra ticket to the Knicks game...
而你必须在有口臭的朋友…
and you had to choose between a friend who smelled...
跟会戳伤你的朋友之间做选择 你会选谁呢？
and one who bruises you, who would you pick?
哇
Wow.
我是超级《尼克队》球迷
Being a huge Knicks fan myself...
我想你们该选 超级《尼克队》球迷一起去
I think you should take someone who's a huge Knicks fan.
好吧
Okay.
就艾力克了
That's Eric.
很高兴能帮上忙 我去抽烟
Glad to be of help. Matches.
我是说你们何不约理查去看球赛？
I meant, why don't you take Richard to the game?
哦
Eh.
什么？
What?
- 我不知道   - 少来了
- I don't know.     - Come on!
他不会乱戳人 而且口气清新
He keeps his fingers to himself, and he's always minty fresh.
理查人不错 但我们跟他不熟
Richard's really nice. Uh, we just don't know him really well.
而且他很老
Plus, he's old...
比一些人老
older than some people.
但比一些建筑物年轻
But, uh, younger than some buildings.
那又怎么样？他年纪有点大 没什么大不了的
So what, he's a little older. Big deal.
他对我来说很重要
He's important to me.
如果你们问他 或许他会开捷豹跑车载你们去
If you ask him, he might take you in his Jag.
我们要怎么答应她
How do we say yes...
同时装做我们不是为了想搭跑车？
and make it seem like it's not just to ride in the cool car?
好吧 这可能有点难
Okay, this could be tough.
好吧 摩妮卡
Okay, okay, okay. Monica?
我们可以带他去 但他一定开捷豹跑车
We'll bring him, but only if he takes the Jaguar.
你差点就成功了
Ooh, you almost had it.
不 尿布没脏
No, no, you're fine. You're fine.
- 哈罗   - 嘿
- Hello, ha, ha.     - Hey.
甜心
Hi, honey. Oh.
你们不会相信发生了什么事
You are not gonna believe what happened!
我们在地上玩 他抓住桌子
We were playing on the floor, and he grabs the table...
自己站起来
and he pulls himself up!
他自己站起来
He pulled himself up!
他站起来了
Standing man!
我很遗憾你们错过了 如果你们想看 我都拍下来了
I'm sorry you missed it, but I did tape it if you wanna see it.
我们知道 上星期他就会那么做
Uh, we know. He already did it last week.
如果你要的话 你可以看我们的录影带
You can watch our tape if you want.
听着 我不敢相信 我错过所有的第一次
Ah, see, I don't believe this. I missed the first time of everything.
他第一次翻身跟爬行
The first time he rolled over, the first time he crawled.
还有什么？他会说话或开车吗？
What else? Has he spoken? Is he driving?
他有最喜欢的酒类饮料吗？
Does he have a favorite liqueur?
他就快会说话了
He is getting closer on the talking thing.
他还不会叫妈妈 但有一次他说"阿姆"
He can't quite say "mama" yet, but once he said "Yemen."
我不知道 我厌倦了老是在错过
See, I don't know. I'm so sick of missing stuff.
我不只要陪他一天 我要陪他一整个周末
I want him for more than a day. I want him for a whole weekend.
听着 我认为…
Listen. I feel...
那应该会很棒
That would be great.
真的吗？我准备了一大套台词
Really? I had a whole speech prepared.
真可惜 那应该会很有趣
Oh, shoot, that would've been fun.
你们看到了吗？
Oh, look, did you just see that?
你们看到了吗？他挥手了
Did you see? He just waved! He just waved!
他不曾挥过手
He's never waved before!
对 他挥过手 太棒了
Yes, he has. Very good.
- 嘿   - 嘿 菲比 你买了什么？
- Hey.     - Hey, Pheebs. What you got there?
《爱的故事》 《挑战不可能》 跟《亲密关系》
Love Story, Brian's Song and Terms of Endearment.
加上《杀戮战场》
Wow, all you need now is The Killing Fields...
跟一些酪梨酱 你就可以办派对了
and some guacamole, and you got yourself a party!
我跟我外婆聊到《老黄狗》的事
I talked to my grandma about the Old Yeller incident...
她说我妈不让我们看悲伤电影结局
and she said my mom used to not show us the ends of sad movies...
不希望我们接触到痛苦与悲伤
to shield us from the pain and sadness.
知道吗？就在她自杀前
You know, before she killed herself.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
理查在哪里？你们甩了他？
Where's Richard? Did you ditch him?
在我们偷了他的午餐钱 还拉他的内裤之后
After we stole his lunch money and gave him a wedgie.
怎么了？他去停车
What's the matter with you? He's parking the car.
- 你们玩得开心吗？ - 你男朋友太酷了
- Did you guys have fun?     - Your boyfriend is so cool.
他让我们开着他的捷豹跑车 乔伊开了12条街 我是15条街
He let us drive his Jaguar. Joey for 12 blocks. Me for 15.
哇
Wow.
他一定最喜欢你
He must like you best.
他给带位员小费那一段呢？
Oh, what about when he tipped the guy who showed us to our seats?
根本没看到他拿出钱
You never even saw the money.
钱德 谢谢你帮我们带位
Hey, Chandler, thanks for showing us to our seats.
不客气 乔伊 谢谢你帮忙停车
Ha, ha, you're welcome. Hey, Joey, thanks for parking the car.
不客气
No problem, ha, ha.
- 钱德   - 我想她们了解了
- Hey, Chandler...     - I think they get it.
大英雄来了
There's the man!
嘿
Hey.
- 你越来越厉害了   - 哈哈
- Hey, you're getting better.     - Huh? Ha, ha.
我要留下这个
I'm gonna keep this.
好吧
Okay.
他把我的钱拿走了
He kept my dollar.
你们第一次离开班去度周末 你们要做什么？
Your first weekend without Ben. What are you doing?
我们要去参观殖民时期的威廉斯堡
Ah, we're going to colonial Williamsburg.
我念大学时认识的一个女孩 是那里的第一位女铁匠
A woman I went to college with is the first female blacksmith there.
殖民时期的威廉斯堡 有点跟不上时代
They're a little behind the times in colonial Williamsburg.
听着 我得走了 不然妈妈要哭了
Ha, ha. Well, look, I better go before Mommy starts weeping.
- 我们爱你   - 再见 妈妈
- We love you.     - Bye, Mommy.
好好玩吧
Have a good time.
好吧 小班
Okay, Ben.
- 罗斯   - 什么？
- Ross.     - Yeah?
快看
Look.
乔伊 你知道我们在这里能看到你吗？
Joey, do you know we can see you from here?
为什么理查这么做就是比我酷？
How come Richard looks cooler with one of these?
或许你得先点雪茄 然后放下铲子
You may wanna light it and lose the spatula.
那真的很可爱 你试着模仿理查
It's cute, you trying to be more like Richard.
我不是在学他
Not like him, per se.
只是不想跟他不一样
Just not unlike him.
他是之前名为钱德的艺人
It's the artist formerly known as Chandler.
我是在尝试新造型
I'm just trying something here, you know?
为什么你不留胡子？
Why didn't you grow a mustache?
我们丢铜板决定
Oh, we flipped for it.
我抽到雪茄 他抽到胡子
I got the cigar, he got the mustache.
如果我们两个都留胡子 看起来会很像呆瓜
If we both grew them, we'd look like dorks.
你们真的不像呆瓜
You really sidestepped that land mine.
我答应理查到楼下跟他碰面
I promised Richard we'd meet downstairs.
你们跟理查有约？
You're meeting Richard?
- 《游骑兵队》比赛   - 他没跟你说吗？
- Ranger game.     - Didn't he tell you?
他说他要跟朋友出去 我不知道他是指你们
He said he was going out with the guys. I didn't know that was you.
你听到了吗？
You hear that?
- 我们是朋友   - 我们是朋友
- We're the guys!     - We're the guys!
他留胡子的样子 让你想起席薇亚阿姨？
With that mustache, he reminds me of Aunt Sylvia.
没错
Thank you!
（中央咖啡厅）
- 嗨 我们来了   - 嗨
- Hi, we're visiting.     - Yay.
小班跟爸爸
It's Ben and his dada.
爸爸
Dada.
- 你会叫爸爸吗？ - 噢
- Can you say "dada"?     - Aw.
我跟你的妈妈们说你会说 所以你非说不可
I'm telling your mommies you said it, so you might as well.
- 运气不好？ - 没错
- No luck, huh?     - No.
刚刚我听到他说二
A while ago, I got a "seh" out of him...
我以为他是说第二照顾者 可是…
which I thought might turn into "seh-condary caregiver," but...
你能帮我抱抱他吗？我得把包包放好
Would you, uh, hold him for a sec? I gotta take this off.
- 好的 没问题   - 来吧
- Oh, yeah, sure, okay.     - There we go.
你在做什么？
What are you doing?
我在抱小班
I'm holding Ben.
对 他是小宝宝 不是炸弹
Yeah, well, he's a baby, not a bomb.
好的
Okay.
像抱足球一样抱着他
Hold him like you'd hold a football.
我都是这样抱足球的
This is how I would hold a football.
来吧 好了
Here. Here. There we go.
抱歉 我不太会带小孩 我一直跟小孩没什么接触
Sorry, I'm not very good with babies. I haven't been around them.
- 我是说从我一岁后   - 哈哈
- I mean, you know, since I was one.     - Ha, ha.
- 没关系 没什么大不了的   - 真的吗？
- It's all right. No big deal.     - Really?
我相信我们生了孩子后 你会有不一样的想法
You'll feel different when it's our baby.
- 什么？ - 什么？
- What?     - What?
你想过那种事了？
You think about stuff like that?
对 我是说…
Uh, yeah. I mean...
事实上我想我们得生两个
Actually, I kind of think that we'll have two babies.
生两个？
Two babies?
你知道的 一男一女
You know, a boy and a girl.
我希望先生女儿 小班才不会有竞争压力
Hopefully, the girl will come first, so Ben won't feel competitive.
之后呢？
Then what's gonna happen?
我们不想让孩子们在城市里长大 所以我们会搬到史卡戴尔
We won't wanna raise kids in the city, so we'll move to Scarsdale.
史卡... 嗯-哼
Scar... Uh-huh.
我们可以远离我们的爸妈 不必看到他们
We'll be far enough from our parents so we don't have to see them...
但距离也够近 他们能来当保姆
but close enough that they can babysit.
对 我知道税率比拿索郡高
And yes, I know the taxes are a little higher than Nassau County...
但学区非常不错
but the school system's great.
哇 哈哈
Wow! Ha, ha.
那真的太棒了
Wow, that's great! Great!
- 好吧 你知道吗？ - 嗯？
- Okay, wow! You know what?     - Hmm?
我的休息时间结束了
I'm off my break now. So, uh...
来吧 你抱着他
Um, here. You take this.
还有 恩...
And, um...
我要去帮这些非常好的人倒咖啡
I'm gonna go pour these very nice people some coffee.
好吧
Okay.
看吧 我没拿咖啡壶
Look at that. I don't have a pot.
我没拿咖啡壶 或许我把咖啡壶放在家里
I don't have a pot. Maybe I've got one at home.
或是放在史卡戴尔了 那是门吗？
Or in Scarsdale. Hey, is that a door?
瑞秋
Rach.
- 嘿   - 菲比 怎么样啊？
- Hey.     - Hey, Pheebs. What's happening?
杀人 癌症 足球队在安地斯山脉吃掉彼此
Oh, okay, murder, cancer, soccer teams eating each other in the Andes.
- 你看了电影？ - 呃
- You watched the movies?     - Uh-huh.
这个世界是怎么了？
What is happening to the world?
我是说…不 因为E.T.离开了
I mean... No, no, because E.T. Leaves...
洛基输了 夏绿蒂死了
and Rocky loses. Charlotte dies.
哪个夏绿蒂？
Charlotte who?
织网的那个 蜘珠夏绿蒂
With the web. The spider.
他死了 他生下宝宝后就死了
She dies. She has babies and dies.
那像是"欢迎出院回家" 然后他死了
It's like, "Welcome home from the hospital." Thud!
你想觉得开心点吗？
You wanna feel better?
- 对   - 好吧
- Yeah.     - Okay.
拿去吧 看这个
Here. Watch this.
《风云人物》 我听过这部电影
It's a Wonderful Life. Yes, I've heard of this.
你一定会喜欢 片名说明了一切
So you can't lose. It's there in the title.
剧情保证美好
Wonderfulness is baked right in.
我被《洋基之光》骗了
I fell for that with Pride of the Yankees.
我以为电影描述《洋基队》的光荣
I thought I'd see a film about Yankee pride.
结果是主角得了路贾里格症
And boom! The guy gets Lou Gehrig's disease.
主角就是路贾里格 你没发现吗？
Uh, the guy was Lou Gehrig. Didn't you kind of see it coming?
看一下那部电影 它会让你恢复对人性的信心
Watch that. It'll restore all your faith in humanity.
嘿 大英雄 比赛时间
Hey, big guy. Game time.
- 嘿 马上到   - 有比赛？
- Hey! Be right there!     - There's a game?
对 我刚去买了戳戳棒
I just got my Pik-Up Stiks back from the shop.
有种放马过来
Bring your nerves of steel.
是篮球季后赛
It's the basketball playoffs.
我真的很高兴 但你不必看在我的面子上陪他们
Um, I appreciate this, but you don't have to hang out with them for me.
他们有彼此的陪伴
They have each other.
不 甜心 别担心
Oh, no, honey. I mean, don't worry.
我喜欢跟他们在一起 他们跟我其他的朋友不一样
I like hanging out with them. They're different than my other friends.
他们不会一开始就说 "你知道谁在铲雪时死掉了吗？"
They don't start sentences with "You know who just died shoveling snow?"
好吧 太棒了 快去吧
All right, that's great. Then just go.
加油 《尼克队》
Go Knicks!
- 是大学篮球季后赛   - 噢
- Uh, it's the college playoffs.     - Oh.
- 那么加油 瓦萨学院   - 他们没有晋级季后赛
- Then, go Vassar!     - Uh, they're not in it.
- 好吧 那么快去吧   - 好的
- Okay, then just go.     - Okay.
为什么我觉得很困扰？
Ugh, why does this bother me so much?
我不是那种想每天24小时 都黏在一起的人
I'm not one of those people who wants to spend 24 hours a day together.
当然
Sure.
只是他的空闲时间不多 我该怎么办？
He just doesn't have much free time. What do I do?
那重要吗？反正你会死掉 离婚或轰掉宠物的头
Does it matter? You'll just die or divorce or blow your pet's head off.
- 恩   - 我也是
- Ugh!     - Me too!
瑞秋 我有个问题 理查又跟他们做计划了…
Rachel, I got a question. Richard made plans again with the guys...
罗斯计划了整个世纪
Ross made plans for the century.
我要去看女性杂志 或许里面提供了一些好方法
I'm gonna go read Cosmo. Maybe there's something helpful in it.
就算没有 我可以学着 用剩下的圣诞节蜡烛做比基尼除毛
If not, I can learn how to do a bikini wax with leftover Christmas candles.
好吧
Okay.
刚刚到底是怎么一回事？
What happened back there?
我不知道 你来告诉我吧
I don't know. You tell me.
前一分钟我像抱足球一样抱着小班 后来发现我会有两个孩子
One minute I'm holding Ben, then I've got two kids...
住在史卡戴尔 抱怨税率问题
I'm living in Scarsdale complaining about taxes!
对不起 我会想很多事
Well, I'm sorry. I think about stuff.
我在工作 组合骨头 思绪开始奔腾
You're at work, you're assembling bones, your mind wanders.
你为未来二十年做计划 我们才开始交往六星期
You've planned out the next 20 years. We've dated for six weeks!
难道你没想过我们的未来吗？
You never think about our future?
对 我会想明天要到谁家过夜
I think about whose apartment we'll sleep at tomorrow...
下星期六要到哪里吃晚餐
and where we'll have dinner next Saturday!
我不会去想我们孩子的名字
I do not think about our children's names!
你知道我们孩子的名字？
You know what our children's names will be?
哈哈 不知
Ha, ha, no.
不 我看过一本书 里面有个女孩叫艾蜜莉
No, I mean, you know. I read a book, and there was a girl named Emily.
我觉得那会是个好名字
And I thought that might be good.
哪本书？
What was the book?
《儿童命名宝典》
The Big Book of Children's Names.
好吧 罗斯
Okay. Ross, Ross.
听我说
Okay, listen.
我们的关系非常棒
What we have is amazing.
但我不要别人帮我决定人生
But I do not want everything decided for me!
我一直都过着那样的生活
I spent my whole life like that.
巴瑞跟我就是那样 所以我才会离开
It's what I had with Barry. That's a reason I left.
现在我不想那样
I like not knowing right now.
抱歉吓到你了 但想跟我在一起 你就得接受
Sorry if that scares you, but if you wanna be with me, deal with that!
- 好吧   - 谢谢
- Okay, fine!     - Thank you!
- 我还没有说完   - 我不知道
- We're not done!     - I didn't know that.
跟你在一起的男人 一直在计划他跟你的未来
You're with a guy who won't stop planning his future with you.
他知道我们一定会在一起
He knows we'll end up together.
如果那吓坏了你 你必须接受
If that scares you, tough! You'll have to deal with that.
- 我会的   - 很好 因为我爱你
- I will!     - Good, because I love you!
是吗？我也爱你
Oh, yeah? I love you too!
- 那是我们第一次那么说   - 对
- That's the first time we've said that!     - Yes.
- 我要吻你   - 快来吧
- I'm gonna kiss you!     - You better!
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
谢谢你推荐的电影
Oh, thanks for the great movie tip.
- 你喜欢吗？ - 对
- Did you like it?     - Oh, yeah.
我不知道我比较喜欢 乔治巴里毁了家族企业
I don't know if I was happier when George Bailey destroyed the business...
还是唐娜里德哭泣 或药剂师害他的耳朵流血
or, um, Donna Reed cried or when the pharmacist made his ear bleed.
我能了解你不喜欢耳朵那一段 但结局不是很棒吗？
I'll give you the ear thing, but wasn't the ending wonderful?
我没看完 我太沮丧了
I didn't watch it. I was too depressed.
剧情越来越可怕 它应该叫：
It kept getting worse! It should've been called:
《去他的鬼人生 你不会相信人生就是这么惨》
"It's a Sucky Life, And Just When You Think It Can't Suck Anymore, It Does!"
踢球 救球 还有…
Kick, save! And...
挡球
denied!
他接到球 越过中线 带球
He gets it back. Pass to the middle, lines it up and bam!
太棒了
Yes!
那一球很漂亮吧？
Could that shot be any prettier?
天啊 你真的太厉害了
Man, you are incredible.
念大学时我们有手足球
We had a table in college.
真的吗？我不知道1800年代有手足球
Oh, really? I didn't know they had foosball in the 1800s.
很不错的胡子 到了青春期后你的胡子会变多
Nice mustache. At puberty, that thing will really kick in.
甜心 我知道这很煞风景 但晚餐准备好了
Not to sound too Florence Henderson, but dinner's on the table.
再一分就好
One more point.
得分
Score!
- 可以走了吗？ - 呃
- Now can we go?     - Uh...
所以我们才不让她玩
That's why we don't let her play.
- 没事吧？ - 恩
- Is everything all right?     - Mm-hm.
啊-哦
Uh-oh.
别生他的气 那都是我们的错
Oh, hey, don't be mad at him. It's our fault.
抱歉我们一直拉着他
I'm sorry we've been hogging his time.
跟他在一起真的很好玩
He's just really great to hang out with.
- 那个嘛   - 不 真的
- Well...     - No, seriously.
我们谈过这个 他比我们的爸爸酷多了
We just talked about this. He is so much cooler than our dads.
我们的爸爸还不错 但理查是…
Our dads are okay and all, but Richard is just...
你干嘛踢我？
Ow, ow, ow. What are you kicking me for?
我在说话
Huh? I'm trying to talk here.
你们把我当成爸爸？
Uh, you guys see me as a dad?
- 对   - 不
- Oh, yeah.     - No!
不
No.
显然你不了解年轻人的词汇
You're just clearly not familiar with our young persons' vernacular.
我们说"爸爸" 事实上是指 "好兄弟"
When we say "dad," we mean "buddy."
- 我们是说"好朋友"   - 对
- We mean "pal."     - Uh-huh, yeah.
不 真的 乔伊是我爸
No, seriously. Joey's my dad.
摩妮卡是我爸
Monica's my dad.
我在公司里还有一些爸爸
I've even got some dads down at work.
那真的很棒
That's fine.
你们的另一个爸爸跟我 要一起度过浪漫夜晚
Well, your other dad and I are gonna go have a romantic evening.
后会有期
I'll just see you kids around.
晚安
Nighty-night.
- 你不是爸爸   - 你不是爸爸
- You're not a dad!     - You're not a dad!
我不敢相信你害我们惹上麻烦
I can't believe you got us into trouble.
你还好吗？
So are you okay?
没事
Yeah.
我只是…
Just...
我觉得自己像是有一百岁了
I feel like I'm about a hundred.
我以为我跟他们一样年轻
I thought I was just one of the guys.
过来
Come here.
我会让你变年轻
I'll make you feel like one of the guys.
唔
Mm.
就一个酷男人来说 你的手足球技巧逊呆了
For a really cool guy, you suck at foosball.
你在说什么？我痛宰他们
I was killing them.
- 对 他们也很逊   - 哈哈
- Yeah, well they suck too.     - Ha, ha.
唔
Hmm.
将便便尿布放在便便尿布桶里
You take the poopy diaper and put it in the poopy diaper pail.
叫它便便尿布 不会让这个过程变可爱
Calling it a "poopy diaper" doesn't make this process any cuter.
- 谁啊？ - 我们回来了
- Hello.     - It's us.
快上来
Come on up.
我去帮他收拾东西
I'll get his stuff together.
好吧 现在我们可以那么做 对吧？小班
Okay, we can do this now, can't we, Ben?
对 我们可以的
Yes, we can.
好了 我办到了
There! I did it!
我办到了
Ha, ha, I did it!
看吧
Ooh, look at that!
完全没有掉下来
Oh, it stays on and everything.
- 嗨   - 嗨
- Hi.     - Hi.
对不起 你说什么？你说"嗨"吗？
I'm sorry. What did you just say? Did you just say "hi"?
天啊 罗斯 小班刚刚说"嗨"
Oh, my God! Ross? Ben just said hi!
- 什么？ - 小班说 "嗨"
- What?     - Ben just said hi!
什么？他说"嗨"？
What, the word "hi"?
不 他在叫海叔
No, my Uncle Hi.
太棒了 我又错过了 我错过了一切
Great! And I missed that too. I miss everything!
对不起 我想我让他有感觉
Oh, I'm sorry. I guess I just bring it out in him.
- 他在哪里？ - 我们想你
- Where is he?     - We missed you.
我们好想你 快过来 小班
We missed you so much! Come here, Ben, ha, ha.
你们猜怎么了？小班说了第一个字
Guess what? Ben just said his first word.
他说什么？
What did he say?
他说嗨
Something about hi.
- 那真的太棒了   - 妈妈以你为荣
- That's so exciting!     - Mommy's so proud of you!
嗨…？
Hi. Hi?
比较像是嗨
You know, actually, it's more like, hi!
- 嗨   - 嗨
- Hi?     - Hi.
- Hi.     - Hi.
这可能得花点时间
This could go on for a while.
你说的对 计程车还在等我们
You're right. We've got a cab waiting.
这真的很有趣
Well, this was fun.
我们下次再来玩吧 小班 你觉得如何？
We should do it again sometime, Ben. What do you say?
好的
Okay.
- 好吧 我何时能去接他？ - 星期二
- All right, so I've got him?     - Tuesday.
大家再见
Bye, you guys.
- 保重   - 再见 小班
- Take care.     - Bye, Ben.
再见
Bye.
他说再见吗？
Did he just say "bye"?
他说再见
He said bye!
你说…他跟我说再见
You said... He said bye to me!
- 对 没错   - 噢
- Yes, he did!     - Oh.
突然间我有种他要去念大学的感觉
Suddenly I'm seeing him go off to college!
我们得走了 计程车还在楼下等
We've gotta go. We've got that cab downstairs.
再见
See you later.
- 再见   - 再见
- Bye.     - Bye.
- 噢   - 哈哈
- Oh!     - Ha, ha.
- 再见   - 再见
- Bye.     - Bye.
再见
Bye.
噢
Oh.
哇 看看我挖的这个大洞 柏特
Wow. Look at this nice deep hole I dug. Hey, Bert...
这个洞很漂亮吧？
isn't this a nice hole here?
好的 恩
Okay, ahem.
小班 这时厄尼把柏特埋在沙里 然后找不到他
Ben, this is the part where Ernie buries Bert in the sand and can't find him.
我用快转看过录影带 后来他又找到他
Now, I've looked ahead on the tape, and he does find him again.
在那之前 发生了一些不好的事
But before that happens, there's some rough going for a while.
我想我们应该可以应付
But I think we can handle it.
还有字母歌 我们知道结局一定会很快乐
And there's just the alphabet, but we know that ends well, so...
来吧
Here we go.
柏特？柏特？
Bert? Bert?
柏特？
Bert?
我朋友柏特怎么了？刚刚他还在这里
What happened to my friend Bert? He was here just a moment ago.
不 我的老朋友柏特不见了
Oh, no! My old friend Bert is lost.
- 恩   - 我很高兴你在这里
- Mm.     - I'm so glad you're here.